<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>



<string name="Rokudou_3_9_1_1"> Pozdravljen, Android.  Sem Rokudou. </string>

<string name="Rokudou_3_9_1_2">
Ever get the feeling that you are on the wrong team, Android?  Ever wonder if maybe Kabochanomizu isn’t exactly the man he portrays himself to be?
</string>

<string name="Rokudou_3_9_1_3"> Zares si izjemen stroj.  Tvoje sposobnosti so predobre za iztrošenega znanstvenika, kot je Kabocha.  Pridruži se moji ekipi. </string>

<string name="Rokudou_3_9_1_4">
I can see that you are hesitant.  Not surprising; I am sure Kabocha did his best to convince you that he’s a kind-hearted scientist, acting for the greater good of the world.  Make no mistake, Android.  Kabocha is a lunatic--he must not gain access to The Source.
</string>

<string name="Rokudou_3_9_1_5"> Pridruži se moji ekipi, Android.  Pomagaj nam poiskati Izvor in spremeniti svet.  Vzemi si nekaj časa za razmislek.  Sem potrpežljiv človek. </string>


<string name="Rokudou_4_1_1_1"> Ne skrbi za Kyla, Android.  Bil je dober agent, vendar je postal domišljav.  V zadnji analizi je bila ošabnost njegova največja slabost.  Ti pa si pokazal zvitost in iznajdljivost.  Odlično! </string>

<string name="Rokudou_4_1_1_2">
The Source has a way of affecting people.  Other teams I sent to this island in the past have vanished without a trace.  The few that made it back returned with fatal health problems.  That’s why an inorganic like you is so perfect for this job.  Make no mistake, The Source is a natural occurrence--nature’s next logical step.  I theorize that it may actually be a tiny piece of a larger whole, a body that created the entire universe!  But there will be plenty of time for academics once we have obtained The Source; for now we must concentrate on finding it.
</string>

<string name="Rokudou_4_1_1_3"> Si premislil o moji ponudbi, Android?  Še vedno velja.  Pridruži se moji ekipi. Pomagaj mi poiskati Izvir in rešiti svet pred blazneži, kot je Kabocha. </string>

<string name="Rokudou_4_4_1_1"> Android.  Časa za vljudnosti ni več.  Kabocha ima Izvor in kmalu bo ugotovil, kako lahko uporabi njegovo moč.  Če ga želimo ustaviti, moramo ukrepati takoj.  Naše edino upanje si. </string>

<string name="Rokudou_4_7_1_1">
My sensors indicate a large disturbance field not far from here.  That must be the location of Kabocha’s secret lab.  He’s surely shielded it, which means the readings I am picking up are actually a tiny fraction of the power he is generating.  It must be The Source!  We must move quickly if we are to stop him and his insane scheme.
</string>

<string name="Rokudou_4_7_1_2"> Ne obupaj, Android.  Usoda sveta je odvisna od tebe. </string>

<string name="Rokudou_final_boss_1_1">
Excellent work, Android.  You have penetrated Kabocha’s secret laboratory.  The Source is within our grasp!
</string>

<string name="Rokudou_final_boss_1_2"> Hitro, znebi se Kaboche.  Morda je star in krhek, vseeno pa je Izvor v nevarnosti, dokler je živ. </string>

<string name="Rokudou_final_boss_1_3"> Android, ne izgubljaj časa!  Uniči Kabocho in vladala bova Zemlji! </string>
</resources>